<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>RStreams Flow on RStreams</title><link>https://rstreams.org/rstreams-flow/</link><description>Recent content in RStreams Flow on RStreams</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 11:02:05 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rstreams.org/rstreams-flow/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Getting Started</title><link>https://rstreams.org/rstreams-flow/getting-started/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 11:02:05 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://rstreams.org/rstreams-flow/getting-started/</guid><description>RStreams flow is powered by the popular Serverless Framework. It has a very large community and many plugins that provide a scaffold for RStreams Flow to build on. The Serverless Framework does have some deficiencies, however, it is believed that it is extensible enough that these can be improved or worked around.
Summary Get up an running to develop with RStreams with the sample app in less than 30 minutes.</description></item><item><title>Project Organization</title><link>https://rstreams.org/rstreams-flow/project-organization/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 11:02:05 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://rstreams.org/rstreams-flow/project-organization/</guid><description>ToC
Summary Root-level Files and Directories Project Serverless File Invoke a bot locally hitting an actual RStreams queue
Summary This doc explains how projects are organized and what all the files are and what they mean, using the example project from the Getting Started Guide.
Root-level Files and Directories Path Description .</description></item><item><title>Running Locally</title><link>https://rstreams.org/rstreams-flow/running-locally/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 11:02:05 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://rstreams.org/rstreams-flow/running-locally/</guid><description>ToC
Summary Prerequisites Project Serverless File Invoke a bot locally hitting an actual RStreams queue
Summary This doc explains how to invoke bots running locally that hit actual queues in a deployed RStreams Bus as well as how to mock out a queue and invoke a bot with that mock data. It also explains how to set breakpoints in your code.</description></item><item><title>Configuring RStreams</title><link>https://rstreams.org/rstreams-flow/configuring-rstreams/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 11:02:05 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://rstreams.org/rstreams-flow/configuring-rstreams/</guid><description>Coming soon.</description></item></channel></rss>