<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>RStreams Flow on RStreams</title><link>https://rstreams.org/rstreams-flow/</link><description>Recent content in RStreams Flow on RStreams</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 11:02:05 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rstreams.org/rstreams-flow/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Getting Started</title><link>https://rstreams.org/rstreams-flow/getting-started/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 11:02:05 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://rstreams.org/rstreams-flow/getting-started/</guid><description>ToC
Summary Install Node and NPM Install the Serverless Framework Get RStreams Bus Config Secret Name AWS Access Create a new project from an RStreams Flow Template Step 1 - Create the project from the template Step 2 - Initialize everything Step 3 - Compile and Run Project Commands using NPM
RStreams flow is powered by the popular Serverless Framework.</description></item><item><title>Running Locally</title><link>https://rstreams.org/rstreams-flow/running-locally/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 11:02:05 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://rstreams.org/rstreams-flow/running-locally/</guid><description>ToC
Summary Prerequisites Things you need to know Invoke a bot locally hitting an actual RStreams queue
Summary This doc explains how to invoke bots running locally that hit actual queues in a deployed RStreams Bus as well as how to mock out a queue and invoke a bot with that mock data.</description></item><item><title>Project Organization</title><link>https://rstreams.org/rstreams-flow/project-organization/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 11:02:05 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://rstreams.org/rstreams-flow/project-organization/</guid><description>ToC
Summary Root-level Files and Directories
Summary This doc explains how projects are organized and what all the files are and what they mean, using the example project from the Getting Started Guide.
Root-level Files and Directories Path Description .mock-data/ Developers put their mock data in this directory.</description></item><item><title>Configuring RStreams</title><link>https://rstreams.org/rstreams-flow/configuring-rstreams/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 11:02:05 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://rstreams.org/rstreams-flow/configuring-rstreams/</guid><description>ToC
Summary RStreams Config Structure RStreams ConfigProviderChain RStreams Config Secrets Manager Secret Approach RStreams Flow Projects Any Type of Project: Environment Variables Environment Variables Approach File Approach
Summary Understand how to provide the configuration that the RStreams SDK needs in order to communicate with an instance of an RStreams Bus.</description></item></channel></rss>