<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>RStreams Node SDK on RStreams</title><link>https://rstreams.org/rstreams-node-sdk/</link><description>Recent content in RStreams Node SDK on RStreams</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 18:19:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rstreams.org/rstreams-node-sdk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Getting Started</title><link>https://rstreams.org/rstreams-node-sdk/getting-started/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 18:19:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rstreams.org/rstreams-node-sdk/getting-started/</guid><description>ToC
Are you setup to run the examples? Principle Operations Write to the bus Write a single object to the bus Write multiple objects to the bus Stream multiple objects to the bus fast
This primer provides exactly enough knowledge of streaming concepts for a developer to successfully
This primer provides exactly enough knowledge of streaming concepts for a developer to successfully write streaming applications using the RStreams SDK and bus.</description></item><item><title>Streams Primer</title><link>https://rstreams.org/rstreams-node-sdk/streams-primer/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 18:19:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rstreams.org/rstreams-node-sdk/streams-primer/</guid><description>ToC
Overview Pipes and Streams Readable Writeable Duplex Transform or Through
This primer provides exactly enough knowledge of streaming concepts for a developer to successfully write streaming applications using the RStreams SDK and bus. It is not intended as an exhaustive treatise on the vagaries of Node streams. We all have work to do.
Overview There truly is nothing new under the sun.</description></item><item><title>Read/Write at Scale</title><link>https://rstreams.org/rstreams-node-sdk/read-write-scale/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 18:19:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rstreams.org/rstreams-node-sdk/read-write-scale/</guid><description>ToC
Overview Reading at Scale App Use Cases and Considerations Config to the Rescue Writing at Scale Considerations Config to the Rescue
You need to understand what a pipe and stream step in a pipe are.
Overview The RStreams Node SDK includes a simple utility function to create pipes and nearly every kind of stream you&amp;rsquo;d need to work with massive amounts of continuously generated data in an instance of the RStreams bus.</description></item></channel></rss>